所以欢迎，
so welcome
嗯，今天我将完成
um today I'm going to go through the
从互联网收集图像
process of collecting image from the
internet
并将它们增强到可以使用
and enhancing them to where you can use
这些图像创建较低模型的过程，嗯，
those to create a lower model
使用 Koya SS GUI 解决方案，
uh using the Koya SS GUI solution so
这样您就可以实际使用您的模型
that you can actually use your models
自动一对一解决方案
using the auto one one one solution
所以我想我们可能会
so I guess we maybe it's I'm going to
为这个视频制作多个部分
make multiple parts for this video the
第一个将是收集
first one is going to be the collection
和准备所有这些
and the preparation for all of those
图像
image
所以让我们开始
so let's start
所以有人建议也许它会
so someone suggested that maybe it would
是 从 1990 年代开始创建 Jennifer Aniston 模型很有趣，
be interesting to create a Jennifer
Aniston model
所以让我们开始
from the 1990s so let's go and let's
收集这些图像，然后
start to collect those image and then
我们将看看我们如何实际处理
we'll see how we actually go and process
它们并将它们处理到可用于
them to a point where they are usable to
创建 Laura 的程度
create a Laura
所以让我们去搜索 Jennifer 安妮斯顿
so let's go and search Jennifer Aniston
和
and
这里有一大堆我们可以
here's a whole bunch of image we can
select
从互联网上选择的图像，通常当我
from the internet and typically when I
去的时候，我会尝试找到高分辨率或
go I try to find high resolution or the
最高分辨率的图像，这些图像
highest resolution image possible that
至少适合 512 x 5 12 像素
will at least fit a 512 by 5 12 pixel
分辨率，这意味着 512 乘以 512 给出 X
resolution meaning 512 times 512 gives X
数 的像素，所以我真的不关心
number of pixels so I don't really care
图像的纵横比，
about the aspect ratio of the image
因为我们将使用像桶一样处理
because we're going to use like
bucketing which will take care of any
我们将要使用的任何纵横比，所以我们
aspect ratios we're going to use so we
不必关心保留它们
don't have to care about keeping them
正方形 它们可以是
Square they can be landscape portrait
横向 纵向 正方形或者都很好 所以让我们从
square or it's all fine so let's start
这个开始吧 我猜它的分辨率相当低
with this one it's a fairly I guess low
我会以这种方式裁剪它
resolution and I would crop it this way
所以这个可能会很小 它是一个
so this one would probably be small it's
潜在可用的但它有点
a potential usable one but it's kind of
柔软 有点像
soft a little bit see it's kind of a
视频捕捉，有点软，所以
video capture it's a little bit soft so
它不是最好的，嗯，
it's not the best
uh one to use
这个看起来稍微好一点，但
um this one appears slightly better but
它仍然充满了人工制品，所以
it's still kind full of artifacts so
它不是最好的，嗯，
it's not really the best uh one to use
这个绝对是 软这个
um this one is definitely soft this one
不太好所以我们需要找到
is not as good so we I need to find
大约 16 张好图像这个看起来
about 16 good image this one looks
还不错所以我要把
rather okay so I'm gonna go and drag
它拖到我要创建的文件夹中
that into a folder that I'm going to
以收集所有这些东西
create to collect all of those things
所以我们走吧 并创建一个新文件夹，
so let's go and create a new folder that
我们将其命名为 Jennifer 我
we're going to call Jennifer
知道，
I understand
我将在其中创建一个名为
and in there I'm going to create a
image well 的子文件
subfolder called image well first of all
夹
I'm going to create the subfolder called
Lore because I want to create a low run
在那里我要创建一个
and within there I'm going to create a
名为 image 的新文件夹，
new folder called image
在该文件夹中我将
and within that folder I'm going to
创建另一个名为
create yet another subfolder called
number of repeats 的子文件夹，我打算
number of repeats that I intend to run
在 16 幅图像上运行，我通常会重复 100 次
so on 16 image I usually do 100 repeats
图像作为一部分 较低的
of the image as part of the lower
交易，在这里我要称呼它为
trading and here I'm going to call that
詹妮弗，
Jennifer
所以我首先知道这个文件夹中有哪些图片，所以
so I know what pictures are in this
folder
the first
现在我终于可以打开那个文件夹了，
so now finally I can open up that folder
现在我们可以开始了，所以我要
and now we're good to start so I'm going
移动那个 稍微在这里所以我
to move that slightly here so what I'm
要做的是我只是去点击
going to do is I'm just going to go and
并将这张图片拖到我的文件夹中
click and drag this image into my folder
所以现在我们有了第一张图片
so now we have the first image there
现在让我们继续四处寻找好的
now let's keep fishing around for good
图片我正在使用谷歌 现在
image to use I'm using Google right now
在某个时候，如果我找不到质量好的图像，我可能会切换到 Bing
at some point I may switch to Bing if I
这个
don't find a good quality image this one
看起来
looks
不错所以这是一个很好的分辨率图像
good so that's a good resolution image
2000 像素 x 3000 像素所以这很好
2000 pixel by 3000 pixel so that's good
所以让我们将它拖到
so let's drag that into
目的地
the destination
并让我们找到更多图像
and let's find more image
1990 年代还有什么好东西
what else could be good from the 1990s
这个看起来不错它是公认的
this one looks good it's well recognized
图像分辨率相当低但我们会在
image rather low in resolution but we'll
我们在那里处理它
deal with it once we are there
嗯
um
还有什么可能我不会捕捉
what else maybe I'm not going to capture
选择图像和增强的整个过程
the whole process of selecting image and
他们但是
enhancing them but
um
这个图像看起来不错所以我们也要
this image looks okay so we're gonna
坚持那个
stick with that one too
[音乐]
[Music]
那个看起来不错
that one looks good
所以我有点试图改变姿势风格
so I'm kind of trying to vary the pose
the style the
面部的嗯角度从
um angles of the face to have like from
像这个一样 不错，因为我们有
like this one is not bad because we have
类似的上半身镜头，这是一个
like kind of upper body shot which is a
很好的方法，因为我们需要其中
good way because we're going to need
一些让模型学习，
some of those for the model to learn
比如除了脸部和
like Beyond just the face and the
肩膀，我们还需要学习
shoulders we need to kind of learn what
模型的外观 嗯，还有
the model looks like
um
什么我们可以看看这个
what else could we look at this one
分辨率相当低的它
that's a fairly low resolution it's too
太低了，比如 2 273 x 364。它不会
low like 2 273 by by 364. it wouldn't
与那个一起工作我想我们已经在相似的脸上看到了这个是的，
work with that I think we have seen this
one above similar looking face
但我不认为 我们有它所以我
yeah but I don't think we have it so I
认为这可能是一个很好的上半身
think that could be a good upper body
拍摄类型的
shot type
图像
image
让我们将它拖到那里
let's drag it there
其他一切都好所以这个是
everything else okay so this one is
不同的空气风格
different air Style
可以正常工作
that will work
它有点暗
okay that's a bit dark
嗯
um that could
现在分辨率太低我们
now the resolution is too low we
不会' 无法裁剪它并获得良好的
wouldn't be able to crop it and get good
结果我不会坚持使用
results I'm not going to stick with that
one
那个分辨率相当低的那个 2 并且
this one fairly low resolution 2 and the
东西已经很好而且这很好
thing already good and this well there
这里可能有一个很好的
could be a good one here
所以让我们选择那个
so let's pick that one
还有什么 这个表面是否有任何
what else is there does that surface any
好的图像
good image
让我们寻找更多
let's look for more
寻找不同风格的
looking at finding different style
不同爪子姿势我想
different Paws poses I guess
它有点柔软但它是
it's kind of soft soft-ish but it's kind
一种不同的姿势让我们尝试使用
of a different pose let's try to work
它让我们把它带到这里我们会看到
with it let's bring it here we'll see
多远 我们可以增强它，也许可以
how far we can enhance it to maybe able
利用它
to make use of it
[音乐]
[Music]
嗯，
um
这个
this one
不错的
not bad
分辨率有点低，但我们
resolution is a little low but well we
可以通过 Uprising 来解决这个问题，
can deal with that
with Uprising it
嗯，
um
就像穿着泳衣一样，
so there's that like in a bathing suit
詹妮弗安妮斯顿看起来真的很像
is that really Jennifer Aniston looks
喜欢
like er
那种不同的风格，我想
kind of different style I guess it could
我们可以把它穿成
we could bring it in
不同的衣服，不同的风格，这
different clothing different style this
是两张照片，另一张不是
one is two pictures and one that's not
我们想要的，
what we want
um
嗯，在列表中，
kind of going down the list here
这张照片不错，
this one is not bad
所以我们有多少 现在我们最多
so how many do we have now we are up to
13 岁。所以我们还需要三张三张更多的
13. so we need three more three more
照片我倾向于坚持 16 张
pictures I tend to stick with 16
照片所以这一张很好
pictures so this one is good
现在我们是 14 岁。
now we're 14.
有点像这张
kind of this
14 15 的照片，
snap 14 15 and what else she looks older
我猜她在这张照片上还有什么看起来更老
on this one I guess
我不知道这是否是一个不错的选择，
I don't know if it's a good choice or
但
not but
我有点想建立一个 1990 年代
I'm kind of trying to build a 1990s
风格的模型，
style model
呃，不是
uh not a
最近的两个版本，所以有点保持
two recent version so kind of keeping
the same
相同的年龄或时代啊，
the same age or era
ah
是的，它有点暗，而且
yeah it's a little bit dark and
这个现在太软了，
what about this one now too soft
我想不是真正的 1990，所以让我们
and I guess not not really 1990 so let's
选择大的
go with big
哦，让我们看看我们是否可以在
oh let's see if we can find something
某个时候找到其他东西当我们选择一些
else sometime when we select some of the
顶级图像时
top image
我们可以
we can get
other
在这里得到其他的这个看起来不错我
ones here this one looks pretty good I
不 不认为我们已经有了那个，所以
don't think we've got that one yet so
现在我们已经下降到 60。好吧，让我们
now we're down to 60. okay so let's
继续吧，就像它不需要
let's go with that like it doesn't need
完美一样，我们可以坚持下去，所以
to be perfect we can stick with that so
现在我们有 16 个图像，我们 可以
now we have our 16 image here and we can
在超大图标中查看它们，这样我们就可以
view them in extra large icons so we can
啊，也许我已经得到了两次 不，
ah maybe I've got this one twice no no
没关系，一切都很好，所以现在让我们开始
okay it's all fine so now let's start
处理这些问题，所以我
the processing aspect of those so what I
倾向于做的是，我通常会启动
tend to do is I usually go in fire up
十亿像素以进行排序 帮助
gigapixel to kind of help with the
提升所有这些图像所以让我们
upresing of all of those image so let's
开始 gigapixel
start gigapixel
我要做的是我将
and what I'm going to do is I'm going to
去拖动每个图像所以让我们
go and drag each of those image so let's
选择第一个我将把它拖到
pick the first one I'm going to drag it
这里 现在你可以看到这是一个
in here and now as you can see this is a
相当低的哇我没有意识到它是
fairly low wow I didn't realize it was
这个 308 x 383 像素的小图像
this little 308 by 383 pixel uh image
实际上非常小是
that's actually shockingly small is it
因为我
because I picked it up from the wrong
在选择图像时从错误的地方拾取它让我们
place when I selected my image let's
仔细检查 这是因为它
double check this because it's
太低了
suspiciously low
我从哪里选的 是的
where did I pick this one from
here
它不应该更大 让
yeah it shouldn't have been larger
我们看看我是否再次将它拖到这里然后
let's see if I drag it here again
我现在更换它
and I replace it
也许它只是给我一个
now maybe it's just giving me a
不是真正
resolution that is not the true
分辨率的分辨率所以让我们放弃 这个
resolution so let's ditch this one close
没有保存就关闭了，
without saving
让我们把它放回这里，
let's bring it back here
这次我们的分辨率更高，
and we're at a better resolution this
所以稍微好一点，
time so it's kind of a little bit better
但我喜欢使用千兆像素来
but I like to kind of use gigapixel to
查看效果如何哦，
see how kind of
因为我的默认设置是
oh it's because my default is is down to
向下采样所以让我们实际把它带到
down sample so let's actually bring it
这里所以现在我可以并排制作它
here so now I can make it side by side
现在你可以查看它之前和之后现在让我们
so now you can view it before and after
把它放在 100 分辨率
now it let's put it at 100 resolution
所以现在你可以看到它如何澄清
so now you can see how it clarifies the
实际的前后图像
actual before and after image
所以我 我要去把它保存
so I'm gonna go and save that
为第一张图片
as the first image
好吧现在让我们带来第二张所以
okay now let's bring the second so what
它在这里做了什么它有点去创建
it does here it kind of goes and creates
一个新版本就像缩放 X2
a new version of that like with scale X2
所以我通常去删除原始
so I usually go and delete the original
图像并保持缩放 在这里，
image and keep the scaled one here so
现在我要为每张图片继续这样做，
now I'm gonna keep doing that for every
image
所以现在这一张，正如你所看到的，它
so this one now as you can see it's
已经使图像更清晰了，所以
already making the image much clearer so
我们要保存
we're gonna save that
我们将使用呃在这种情况下
we're going to use the uh in this case
我是 将指定 jpeg，因为它是
I'm going to specify jpeg because it's a
一个 webp 图像，如果您
it's a it's a webp image and if you
不选择 jpeg，它会将其保存
don't select jpeg it's going to save it
为 tiff，并且
as a tiff and that doesn't work too well
创建 Laura 效果不佳，所以现在完成了，让我们
to create the Laura so now that's done
let's bring the
开始吧 并删除
let's go and delete
好让我们把所有的想法都带来让我们
well let's bring me with all the ideas
let's bring the other picture in
现在把另一张图片带进来，你可以看到之前和之后它
now as you can see before and after it's
肯定更好所以让我们保存
definitely better so let's save
继续前进
move on
所以让我们把所有的东西都带进来所以
so let's I'll bring all of them in so
我们有一个快速的交易所以 我将
that we have one quick deal so I'm going
带来我们目前拥有的所有不同图像，
to bring all of the different image
that we have so far
and
正如您所看到的，它在澄清方面做得相当不错，而
as you can see it does a fairly decent
不是
job at clarifying so instead of going
一张一张地尝试查看
one by one and trying to kind of look at
所有图像，我是 只是去
all of the image I'm just going to go
批量转换它们
and batch convert them
嗯
um
所以这里有几张图片，
so there's a couple of image here that
uh
嗯是的我可能必须一张一张地看这个
yeah I might have to go one by one this
我们已经完成了所以我想现在
one we've already done so I think now
我们已经完成了第四张，也就是
we're done down to the fourth which is
这张 所以我很好，我们将保存
this one so I'm good we're gonna save
这张与
this image
Source 相同的图像，从旁边转到这里，
same as Source kind of going here on the
看看
side and looking at
它是哪一张，所以它是 Web P 还是
which one it is so is it a web P that's
JPEG，没问题我们可以保留让我们看看
a JPEG that's fine we can Preserve
这个
let's look at this one
哦 根本没有太大变化
oh it doesn't change at all that much
它仍然相当模糊我想这是
it's still fairly fuzzy I guess that's a
图像的局限性我们将
limitation of the image well we're going
看看我们是否可以做一些事情
to see if we can do something about that
after
无论如何让我们现在增强它
anyway let's enhance it for now
这是一个相当高分辨率的图像
this is a fairly high resolution image
我们应该 不需要用它做太多是的
we shouldn't need to do too much with it
它实际上并没有做太多
yeah it doesn't actually do much with
所以我们将跳过下
that so we're gonna skip over
一个它是一个相当大的分辨率
next one it's a fairly large resolution
所以我们甚至不要在这个上工作
so let's not even work on this one
呃这个
uh this one
我们要走了 裁剪它因为它有点太紧太
we're gonna go and crop it because it's
宽所以对于
a little bit too tight too wide so for
我想去的主题并裁剪
the subject I want to go and crop all of
我的所有图像以将
my image to kind of focus all of the
培训师的所有注意力集中在
attention of the trainer on the subject
我正在尝试训练的主题上你不
that I'm trying to train you don't
真的很关心
really care about the rest of the stuff
她周围的其他东西，我最重要的
around her and what I what what matters
是这个主题看起来不错所以现在我们
is that the subject looks good so now we
要保存它所以我
have we're going to save that so I
现在几乎不得不回去裁剪所有
almost have now to go back and crop all
其他的因为我忘记了
the other ones because I forgot to
实际上
actually
对所有其他的都这样做所以让我们
do that for all the other ones so let's
回到第一个这里让我们裁剪
go back here on the first one let's crop
它因为周围有一些我不关心的东西
it because there is stuff I don't care
about around
现在我实际上可以看到这个图像
and now I can actually see this image
但它有点失败因为我想我
and it kind of fails because I guess I
更换了 原来
replaced the original
的 2x 所以我想我必须
with the 2x so I guess I would have to
去删除那个并带回
go and delete that one and bring back
the
我已经拥有的高档版本
upscale version that I've already got
现在我将继续并
and now I'm just going to go ahead and
裁剪它
crop that
所以你可以看到它可以是
so as you can see it can be a little bit
这样做有点乏味，但
of a tedious work to do that but it's
值得删除和调整
well worth dropping and adjusting
所有内容，这样可以保存图像，所以
everything so saving the image
现在这个是什么，所以我们需要
okay so now what is this one so we need
处理那个，所以让我们先裁剪它，
to deal with that one so let's crop it
这样我们就可以继续了 并
first so we're going to go ahead and
裁剪到这一点，所以我们尽可能多地保留
crop to this point so we keep as much as
原始图像，
the original image as possible
所以现在我们有更好的
so now we have a better
裁剪效果，所以让我们保存图像，
crop so let's save the image
嗯，好吧，
um okay
那么这个呢，所以我们
so what about this one so this one we
可以稍微裁剪一下
can crop slightly
复制废话，我想我不 我真的不
copy crap here I guess I don't really
关心部分裁剪，
care about the part crop
现在
and now save
在这里保存同样的东西肯定有
same thing here there's definitely a lot
很多裁剪需要进行
of cropping that needs to take place
我们将在这里裁剪在那里裁剪
we're going to crop here crop there
然后我们将结果保存
and then we're gonna save the resulting
到 X 版本
to X version
这个呃我们 有点已经做了
this one uh as we sort of already did it
它已经按照我们想要的方式裁剪了所以
it's already cropped as we want so and
我们需要进入并使用这个
we need to go in and work with this one
让我们看看那个裁剪明智它
let's look at that one cropping wise it
看起来不错
looks good
所以我认为分辨率明智我们已经
so I think resolution wise we're already
非常好所以不需要真正抓住
pretty good so no need to really grip
我会按下它，所以这是一个 webp
I'll press that so this one is a webp
我们需要注意
we're gonna need to watch out a little
一点，确保我们将它保存为裁剪后的
bit for it make sure we save it as a
jpeg，
jpeg
所以我总是留下
cropped around so I always leave a
一点边框，因为分桶
little bit of a border because bucketing
实际上是要 去
is actually going to go and change
稍微改变或稍微损坏以适应
slightly or corrupt slightly to fit
within a 64 pixel by 64 pixel limits
分辨率内的 64 像素 x 64 像素限制，这样可以给我
within the resolution so that gives me
一些游乐场，而不会在它
some playground without losing too much
of the subject when it's going to do
要这样做或是否必须这样做时丢失太多主题所以让我们
that or if it has to do that
看看是否 这不是太大没关系好吧
so let's see if this isn't too big it's
fine okay
下一个是这个我们已经完成
next one is this one we've already done
了所以不需要重做
it so no need to redo it
下一个是一个
next one is
小的
that one that's a small one
肯定需要
definitely need to
升级所以
upres that so
所以这个我们要走了
so this one we're gonna go and
放下它
drop it
好吧我们要保存它
okay we're gonna save it
这个
this one
我们可以裁剪顶部的尖刺所以我们真的不会
we can crop the top spiky so we don't
让所有的东西都
really keep all of that stuff cracked a
向右裂开一点
little bit to the right
好吧保存图像
okay save the image
这个很多裁剪
this one lots of cropping to do
做好这个看起来 相当大，除非我
okay this one looks fairly big unless I
需要购买 是的，我需要裁剪它 是的，其中
need to buy yeah I need to crop it
一些非常大，我的意思是
yeah some of those are very big I mean
我们不需要那么大的图像，呃，
we don't need that big of an image uh
这个希望将从
this one hopefully will benefit a lot
裁剪和起义中受益匪浅，但
from cropping and from Uprising but
我不 知道我们会看看我是否裁剪它
I don't know we'll see if I crop it what
之前和之后的样子
does it look like before and after
没什么不同 几乎在它
nothing much different
并排之后看起来更糟
almost looks worse after it's been
嗯，也许是因为我 50 岁，
abreast uh maybe it's because I'm at 50
如果我去 100 是的，
if I go to 100
yeah
让事情更清楚一点
kind of make things a little bit clearer
但它有点带出噪音
but it kind of brings out the noise
也许我可以消除这里设置中的更多噪音
maybe I can remove the bit more noise in
the the setting here
我不知道
I don't know that it does much
如果我将它推到最大它会起到多大作用
if I push it to the max
确实有点帮助我们会
kind of does help a little bit we'll
我们会的 继续吧，我们将不得不
we'll go with that we'll we'll have to
稍微修改一下它，它有点像
rework that one a little bit it's kind
of
在丑陋的一面构建它，所以
build it on the ugly side so this one
我认为它是腐败的，而
I think it's corrupt right and the
这个的解决方案是什么，是
resolution for this one was what for was
的，我想它不是 很好，
yeah I guess it's well not good
这个非常好，
this one very good
不需要裁剪
no need to crop
保存它
save it
和最后一个，
and final one
因为我们已经这样做了，所以我们不需要
as we already did so we don't need to
重做那个好吧，所以现在我们应该拥有我们
redo that one okay so now we should have
在 Upper upres 版本中需要的几乎所有图像，
pretty much all the image we need in
所以现在让我们把
Upper upres versions so now let's bring
那个 让我们清理
that up and let's clean up the content
文件夹的内容
of the folder
所以我们不关心那个图像现在我们
so we don't care about that image now we
只想要裁剪版本所以我们
just wanted the crop version so we're
要删除这两个在这里我
going to delete those two and here I
真的不关心这些我
don't really care about these ones I
想要裁剪 这是最后
want the crop version which is this last
一个版本所以让我们把
one so let's take those
那个放大了两倍我猜它并
uh this one scaled twice I guess it
没有真正使它成为一个巨大的
didn't really make like that's a huge
图像它对外观和感觉没有太大帮助
image it didn't help much with the look
所以我们将删除
and feel so we're just going to delete
放大的那个 这个我们没有
the upscaled one this one we didn't
升级它已经足够大了这个
upscale it's already big enough this one
我们做了所以这个我们放弃了这个我们做了
we did so this one we dropped
什么让我们看看
this one we did what let's see double
双双交换比例版本这是
double swap scale version this is the
旧的
old one
webp 删除这个是招募
webp delete this one was the recruit
版本这个被裁剪得很好 这个是
version this one was pretty cropped this
歌剧，
one was operas
这个是并排的，
this one was abreast
这个是 web P 我们去掉了，
and this one was web P we get rid of
所以这个可能被压了，
so this one was maybe get a pressed
我想我们去掉了这个，
and I guess we get rid of this one
因为它被裁剪了，所以现在我们有
because it was cropped so now we have
16 张图像
the 16 image
准备好了 去吧，但有一
kind of ready to go but there's one
件事可以做，其中一些看起来
thing that could be done some of them
很糟糕，如果我们
may look fairly bad like if we look at
在这里看它们，这个看起来很锋利，所以
them in here this one looks sharp so no
不需要做任何事情，这个看起来锋利
need to do anything this one looks sharp
锋利，这个很软，所以这个可能
sharp this one is soft so this one could
需要一些返工
need some rework and what I tend to try
在这种情况下，我倾向于尝试做的是返回
to do in this case is I go back
并启动 Koya SS GUI
and I fire up the Koya SS GUI
我已经在访问方式中安装了它，因此
I've installed it in way access so
启动了 gooey ear gui.ps1
firing up the gooey ear gui.ps1
外部
foreign
扩散实际上帮助我
diffusion to actually help me
清理了一些 这些图像实际上
clean up some of those image actually
不是钱不想要这个我
not that money don't want this one I
想
want to
用一个一个一个
use out of one one one
所以
so
也许让我们看看是否有任何新东西
maybe let's see if there's anything new
哦是的有一些更新
oh and yes there are some updates
让我们启动网络用户界面
let's fire up the web UI
嗯
hmm
需要一点时间来开始
takes a little while to start
希望 对于我为
hopefully with everything that I'm
音频和屏幕
running for the audio and the screen
截图运行的所有内容，它不会使
capture it's not going to make the
系统
system
过载但
overloaded but
应该没问题所以让我们放慢
should okay so let's Slow it Up
速度自动一对一网络用户界面我
the auto one one one web UI and what I'm
要做的是进入图像 图像
going to do is go into image to image
，我将去删除
and I'm going to go and drop a copy of
我想要更改的图像的副本，所以
that image that I want to change so what
我倾向于坚持使用最大
I tend to do is stick with a maximum
分辨率，在这种情况下它高于
resolution in this case it's higher than
宽度，所以我将使用 1 10 24
width so I'm going to go with 1 10 24
然后我将宽度调整到
and then I adjust the width up to a
适合分辨率的点
point where it kind of fits within the
所以现在我们有一个很好的适合我
resolution so now we have a nice fit I'm
将运行剪辑询问以获得对
going to run clip interrogate to get
kind of a nice
图像是什么的很好的描述
description of what the image is
并且
and
很可能 圣经
it's quite likely that there's already a
中已经有一些关于詹妮弗安妮斯顿的知识，
some knowledge of Jennifer Aniston in
所以我要
the Bible so I'm going to invoke
for Aniston
在描述中引用安妮斯顿，我要做的
in the description and what I'm gonna do
是将去噪强度保持在
is kind of keep the denoising strength
相当低的水平，比如 30%，所以它是
fairly low like at 30 percent so it's a
0.3 的值，我 我要请求
0.3 value and I'm going to ask for a
picture to picture
该图像的图片到图片的再现所以它所做的
rendition of that image so what that did
是
is it kind of
重新构想它根据此处的描述重新构想该图像
reimagined it reimagined this image
based on the description here
并且它将创建该图像的清晰版本，
and it will create a crispr version of
它看起来仍然很像
this image that still looks a lot like
原始图像 现在你必须
the original now you have to kind of
比较一下，从外观的角度来看，这个版本是否可以接受，
compare it is this version acceptable
所以如果我把
from a look perspective so if I bring
原来的版本带到这里，我们把
the original one here and we kind of
它们像那样带来，然后我把它缩小，
bring them like that and I scale it down
这样我们就有了一种更接近
so we have like a kind of closer
匹配的分辨率，
matching resolution
嗯，
um
怎么做 他们比较
how do they compare
好我认为眼睛耳朵有点
well I think the eye ear is a little bit
时髦我认为允许
funky I think the strength of allowing
软件重新想象
the software to kind of re-imagine that
图像的强度有点太强了所以让
image is a little bit too strong so
我们回过头来将
let's go back and let's change that
去噪罢工更改为大概 20 以便
denoising strike to maybe 20 so to limit
真正限制软件可以做什么
really what the software can do
um
所以它会减少它的改变但它
so it's going to change it less but it's
看起来更像原始
going to look more like the original
模型
model
我可以做的事情因为现在我有
something I can do because now I've got
低去噪罢工是我要
the low denoising strike is I'm going to
提高
raise
实际的采样步骤 更高的
the actual sampling steps to higher
采样步骤以获得更好的结果并将
sampling steps to get better results and
采样方法更改为 DPM
change also the sampling method to DPM
plus sde 相机，
plus plus sde cameras
这往往会产生更好的输出所以
which tend to produce better outputs so
希望
hopefully with that
我们会得到一个更好的版本
we're gonna get a much nicer version of
uh 改进的稳定扩散
the uh of the improved stable diffusion
版本 原始图像
version of the original image
所以现在眼睛看起来
so now the eyes look a little bit better
比以前好一点
than they used to
它不那么柔软它仍然不是很
it's not as soft it's still not very
锐利但
sharp but
嗯它确实略有改善我猜
um it does improve slightly and I guess
分辨率错误是的所以
the resolution the errors and yeah so
我们会坚持下去所以我 我
we're gonna stick with that so what I'm
现在要做的是
going to do now is I'm just going to go
回到我的 Jennifer Aniston
back into my Jennifer Aniston
文件夹，
folder
然后将
here and I'm just going to go and drag
这张图片拖回那里，然后
this image back in there and I'm going
删除
to go and delete
副本，这样原来的就可以了 版本
the duplicate so that original version
不见了，现在我要保留
is gone and now I'm going to keep that
那个，所以让我们继续看另一张
one so let's keep looking at the other
图片，
image
这个看起来不错，但是
this one is sort of looking good but
是的，我想我们会保留它，因为
yeah I guess we're gonna keep it as is
这个很安全，这个很好
this one is safety good this one is good
这个 一个很好，一个很好，一个
this one is good that one's good that
很好，可以正常工作，一个
one's fine that works okay that one is
绝对不好，
definitely bad
嗯，让我们尝试改进这个，
um let's try to improve this one
所以我将再次回到这里进入
so I'm going to go back here again into
主要扩散或白色 UI 将
staple diffusion or the white UI drag
图像拖动到这里然后我们是 将
the image here and then we're going to
尺寸调整到最合适所以
go in size it to be the best fit so
我们要去这里我们有点
we're gonna go to here we're kind of
失去
losing
part of
头部或者我宁愿
the heads or I'm gonna I would rather
失去侧面的一些东西而不是
lose some things on the side than
高度的东西
something on the height of the of the
井的也许我会失去一些头
well maybe I could lose some of the head
它不是那么糟糕我想我会
it's not so bad I guess I'm going to
坚持那个现在我们要
stick with that one and now we're going
重新运行审讯剪辑所以我
to go and rerun interrogate clip so I'm
要继续复制 在这里命名
just going to go ahead and copy the name
here
他们是 eclip 以获得更
they're eclip to get a description
接近图像的描述
closer to what the image is about
，现在我们将要求
first and now we're going to ask for a
重新创建该图像
re creation of that image
所以现在我们肯定有一个大大
so now we have definitely a much
改进的版本，
improved version of the noisy image that
我们从开始的嘈杂图像 所以绝对是一个
we started from so definitely an
改进，所以我们要坚持并
improvement so we're gonna stick and
保留那个图像，而不是
keep that image instead of the noisy one
我们添加的嘈杂图像，我们甚至可以尝试
that we add well we could even try to
使用更好的改进，
play with even better Improvement right
这样我就可以尝试 25
that was that so I could maybe try at 25
% 的
percent
去噪强度
denoising strength
，让我们看看 如果拍摄
and let's see what it gives us if the
对象看起来仍然像原来的那样，这会给我们带来
subject still looks like the original
什么，这才是最重要的，
that's what that's what matters
尤其是面部，这是我们
especially the face right that's what we
最关心的，面部看起来
care the most about that the face looks
仍然像同一种微笑，
still like the same kind of smile and
鼻子和眼睛，
nose and eyes
如果它们变得太不同的话，它 有点
if they get too different and it kind of
破坏了实际的模型，所以这个现在
breaks the actual model so this one now
看起来不错，
looks pretty good
所以我认为我们可以使用那个模型，
so I think we are okay to use that one
所以现在您对
so now you have a feel for what is the
从互联网引入图像的工作流程有什么感觉，
workflow to bring in image from the
这可能不够好，也可能不够
internet that may or may not be uh
好 使用然后
good enough to use and then kind of uh
使用 gigafixel 提升这些图像以
lean up those image using gigafixel to
提高分辨率然后查看
improve the resolution and then look at
实际的
the actual
um
图像本身并在稳定扩散中改进它们
image themselves and improve them in
如果它们不够
stable diffusion if they are not
好
good enough
所以我认为现在我们有一个很好的
so I think right now we have a good
起点所有 实际图像看起来
starting point all the actual image look
可用，它们有不同的风格，
usable they are kind of different styles
不同的背景，不同的
different background different
个性，其中
personalities
and
一个仍然困扰着我，
that one is still bugging me right that
一个软到某种程度，我不
one is soft to a point where I don't
知道它会对我们将保留的模型产生什么影响
know how it's going to have an impact on
the model we'll keep it
因为我又想，有时候
because like again I guess sometimes it
如果其中一个
doesn't really matter if one of them is
不好，你显然想要追求完美并不重要，
bad you want to aim for Perfection
但有时你就是
obviously but sometimes you just can't
做不到，这个有一些我
get it this one has something I don't
不太喜欢的东西，让我们重新运行它 再次只是
quite like about it let's rerun it again
为了
just for the sake of
尝试改进，让我们在这里重新运行它
trying to improve things let's rerun it
in here
是的，看起来很合适所以
yeah that looks like in good fit so
让我们重新运行剪辑审讯是的，
let's rerun the clip interrogate
那个图像有些东西
yeah there's something about that image
不太适合我，
that doesn't quite fit well with me
如果是空气，你就去吧 有点
you go if it's the air that kind of are
吵，或者有些地方不对劲，
sort of noisy or
there's something that just doesn't sit
right
所以这个看起来确实有所改进，
so this one looks improved definitely
看起来像是
looking like
稍微
slightly
好一点的版本，也许我需要改变
better version maybe I need to change
这个裁剪并调整大小，这样它就不会
this crop and resize so it doesn't maybe
像它一样被压扁了
squash squish it a little bit like it
做到
did
了，也许我应该将强度降低
and maybe I should reduce the strength
到 20。让我们再重新运行一次
to 20. and let's rerun it one more time
好吧，
okay
所以我认为这很好，让我们
so I think that's pretty good let's keep
that
保留它，让我们把它分解
let's break this here
成
into the
图像，让我们删除重复项，
image and let's delete the duplicate
所以现在我认为我们可以移动了 进入
so now I think we're good to move on to
下一阶段，我们需要为
the next stage which is we need to
这些图像添加说明，我们需要添加一些
caption those image we need to add some
说明，这样我们就可以教
captioning so that we can teach
或训练 Laura 呃关于这个
uh or train the Laura uh about the
主题，而不是
subject and not about things that are
图像中不重要的东西，所以
not important within the image so what
我要做什么 要做的是我要去
I'm going to do is I'm going to go and
复制这条路径，所以我要复制它，
copy this path so I'm going to copy that
然后在这里我们将进入我们的
and then here we're going to go into our
实用程序，在 blip 字幕下，
utilities under blip captioning
我将去粘贴
and I'm going to go and paste the
我们有的目录 我们
directory where we have the image we
想要获得文字说明的图像 我
will want to get text captioning I'm
很好 我正要将
good I'm just going to go and add
Jennifer Aniston 作为前缀添加到每个说明中
Jennifer Aniston to each of the captions
as a prefix
，让我们仔细检查我是否有
and let's double check that I've got the
正确的 Jennifer Aniston 这是正确的
right Jennifer Aniston that's the right
语法 一切都很好所以我们要
syntax that's all good so we're gonna
坚持下去所以我要把它做成
keep with that so I'm gonna make it a
一批 Tate 只是为了做一个漂亮的整数
batch of Tate just to make a nice round
我要做一批八个
number I'm going to do a batch of eight
我要用 10 个光束运行 uh top P90 I
I'm gonna run with 10 beams uh top P90 I
想要为实际字幕获得至少 22 个标记的长度，
want to get a minimum length of 22
tokens for the for the actual
我将点击字幕，所以
captioning I'm going to hit caption so
现在它要做的是
now what it's going to do it's going to
开始字幕，如果我回到
go and start captioning if I go back
这里，它将在
here it's loading the captioning within
Koya SS
the Koya SS
I 中加载字幕 猜测终端
I guess terminal
作为输出，当它开始为
as the output and as it starts
事物添加字幕时，它会开始在
captioning things it will start to show
up
每个图像旁边显示它的文本文件，
it's text files beside each of the image
应该很快开始所以现在
that should start pretty soon so now
它已经完成了 16 个中的 15 个所以现在你
it's got 15 done out of 16 so now as you
可以看到我们开始有字幕
can see we start to have captions
在每张图片旁边，
beside every image
让我们等待它完成，
let's wait for it to be done
现在我们完成了，所以我们
and now we're done so we have captions
在每张图片旁边都有标题，所以您
beside each of those image so what you
现在需要做的是打开每个
need to do now is open up each of those
文本文件
text files
，让我们说打开
and you want to let's say open up the
图片 在更大的视图中，
image in in a larger View
这样你就可以看到标题是什么
so you can see what is being captioned
所以这里詹妮弗安妮斯顿是一个摆姿势拍照的女人，
so here Jennifer Aniston a woman posing
我们真的不在乎
for a picture we don't really care about
摆姿势拍照它穿着一件
posing for a picture it's posing in a
很好的黑色连衣裙和一条紧身
black dress that's fine and a tight
黑色
black
紧身裤
tights
不太确定 那是什么意思 我只是
not too sure what that's about I'll just
去赢她的臀部，
go to win with her ends on her hips
这很好，她还戴着
that's fine and she she's also wearing
手镯 我想我们不会
it bracelets I guess we're not gonna
关心这个，所以没关系，所以我
care about that so that's fine so I
认为现在的描述非常
think this description now is pretty
准确，所以让我们继续 转到下一个
accurate so let's move on to the next
与此文件配套的文本文件
text file that goes with this one
詹妮弗·安妮斯顿 一个穿着
Jennifer Aniston a woman in a black and
黑白裙子的女人，很好 呃
white dress that's fine uh posing
背景中有一个男人
with a man in the background
with a blurry man
背景中有一个模糊的男人 这看起来
in the background that kind of looks
像是准确的描述
like accurate description
所以让我们保存
so let's save this
下一个 图片
next image
Jennifer Aniston 穿着无肩带 yeah
Jennifer Aniston in the strapless yeah
posing
在背景中的一群人面前摆姿势 把
in front of a group of people
in the background
okay
next
so Jennifer Aniston a Woman in a Black
Top like that's kind of a yeah it's kind
of Blackish let's not get too too picky
所有坐着的
about the color and it blacked up any
粉红色
pink
和
and
白色裙子涂黑
white skirt sitting
我不知道它是
I don't know if it's a ledge on the
前面喷泉的壁架还是什么是的，这是一个非常好的
front fountain or something yeah that's
喷泉，在喷泉的壁架上非常好
a fountain that's pretty good on the
ledge of a fountain
呃在背景中是的，这
uh within the background yeah that's
很好让我们把它留到
good let's keep it to that
下一张图片
next image
詹妮弗·安妮斯顿，一个站在
Jennifer Aniston a woman standing in a
厨房里的女人，双手叉腰，是
kitchen with her hands on their hips
的，
yeah
这就是它发疯的地方 hipster
and that's where it went nuts hipster
hipster 哦，是的，让我们摆脱
hipster oh yeah let's get rid of that on
我们手上的那个，
our hands
嗯，
uh
with the
背景模糊，
blurry background
好吧，但她穿着一件白色的
okay but she's wearing kind of a white
T 恤 女人站着，
T-shirt a woman standing it and wearing
身穿
a woman wearing
白色
White
衬衫的女人
shirt
站在厨房里，这很酷好吧，这是
standing in a kitchen that's cool okay
很好的描述是的，你
that's good description yeah you always
总是想描述一下衣服，
kind of want to describe the clothing as
这样你就喜欢你了
well right so that you have like you
这是你可以分辨
kind of this is the way you can tell
稳定扩散的方式 有点忽略那些
stable diffusion to sort of ignore those
东西
things
呃下一个所以现在我们有詹妮弗
uh next one so now we have Jennifer a
一个女人的特写镜头不不不
close-up of a woman holding no no no no
不不不是网球支架我不确定
no not a tennis bracket I'm not sure
它不是网球场但有
like it's not a tennis court yet there's
一个像链条一样的围栏 - 链接栅栏，但
a fencing like a chain-link fence but
关闭了一个
close up of a woman
穿着
wearing
花裙子的女人
a flowery dress
花裙子
flower dress
白色
the white
我认为
I think
with
blurry
背景模糊
background
哦让我们看看
oh let's see
叮当声
jingling sense
好吧 向下
okay
移动到下一个
moving down to the next one
哦，
oh singing
她双臂交叉唱歌 穿着灰色上衣
with her arms crossed wearing a gray top
和棕色裤子 是的，这很好
heavy and brown pants yeah that's good
只有一件
just one
红色的连体衣走在街上，
red body suit walks down the street with
a
h
手里拿着一朵花，这很好，一件
Flowers in her hand that's good
红色的兔子服，是的，已经
a red bunny suit yeah that's
足够了，下
good enough
一件
next one
那个
what's up with the woman
穿着黑白相间的裙子，
wearing a black and white dress with a
脸上带着微笑的女人怎么了，我不在乎
smile on her face I don't care for
面部表情 眼睛颜色 头发
facial expressions eye colors hair
颜色 因为我们想保留
colors because we want to retain the the
她拥有的那些所以我们不打算
ones that she has so we are not going to
指定任何东西 因为如果我们这样做那么
specify anything because if we did that
then
软件就会开始有点
the software would start to kind of
忘记微笑并且它不会
forget about the smile and it wouldn't
真正学习 太好了，所以我
really learn that too well so I would
宁愿保留它，
rather keep that
um
因为我不希望它专注于
because I don't want it to focus on
那些衣服，所以通过提供
those clothing so by giving information
有关衣服的信息，它将学习
about clothing it's going to learn that
并将该衣服与令牌相关联，
and Associated that clothing to the
所以除非我们在哪里指定
Token so unless where we specify that
衣服的颜色和款式 它不会
color and style of clothing it's not
强制执行它，呃，我
going to kind of enforce it on uh I
猜是提示的输出，所以这就是
guess outputs of prompts so that's how
你如何让它忘记
you kind of make it forget about things
你不关心的关于
that you don't care for about the
主题的事情
subject
保存这个这个这个
save this one
这个
this one
可以与
okay with the black dress that's okay
我们的黑色连衣裙一起使用 双臂交叉，看着
with our arms crossed and looking at the
相机，
camera that's all right
蓝色背景，很好，完美的
with a blue background good perfect
描述，
description
下一个
next one
特写，一个女人
close up of a woman
穿着裙子，所以
wearing a dress so wearing a I guess
it's a white dress wearing a
sort of whitish dress and holding into
穿着 香烟 呃
all she's not holding a cigarette
不 她不抽烟 一个
uh no she's not smoking a cigarette
吃香烟的人 我们要打电话 我们要让
eater and we're gonna call we're gonna
make this um
blurry of people
in the background in the
背景中的人变得模糊
in the background
blurry background
next one
with her hands on her hips yeah
with a green
pertain
background
ready
是的，
yeah okay
下一个
next one
女人摆姿势拍照，手
woman posing for a picture with her hand
放在头上 是的，没关系，
on their head yeah that's all right
脖子上戴着项链 是的，没关系，
and a necklace on her neck yeah that's
穿着
all right wearing
坟墓 一件
a grave
漂亮的裙子
a great dress
詹妮弗欧内斯特和一个穿黑裙子的女人
Jennifer Ernest and a Woman in a Black
Dress posing
在红地毯上摆姿势 我 猜猜所以
on the red carpet I guess so
我在电影节上有一个红地毯活动
I have a red carpet event
是的
on the film festival yeah
听起来不错
sounds good
喷射炉然后再次关闭一个
jet furnace then close up a woman with
长头发的女人我不在乎
long hair again I don't care about the
头发的长度
length of the hair
穿着露肩裙
wearing a strapless yeah dress and
看着相机
looking at the camera
我猜她是 不是真的看着
I guess she's not really looking at the
相机我们会看到一个模糊的
camera we're gonna see a blurry
离题
digress
好吧
okay
在皮革的时候是的我猜这是在
when in a leather yeah I guess that's
litter in a letter dress
posing for a picture on a red carpet of
电影院的红地毯上摆姿势拍照的字母连衣裙的垃圾是的
a movie
theater
yeah
没关系听起来不错所以
that's okay that sounds good so the uh
呃 黑色
the black
字母地址
letter address
很好我想就是这样
good I think that's it
所以我们现在已经验证了每个图像的标题
so we have now validated the caption of
each of those image
所以在这一点上我们几乎
so at this point we're pretty much going
准备好进入培训的第二阶段
to be ready to move on to phase two of
这将涉及
the training which is going to involve
配置 kovia  SS Laura 选项卡
configuring the kovia SS Laura tab
实际学习 Dreamboat 所以让我们
to actually learn the Dreamboat so let's
uh
在一个单独的视频中做到这一点
do that in a separate video
希望你喜欢如何实际
hope you enjoyed how to actually
配置和收集图像并
configure and collect the image and
提高质量以准备训练
improve the quality to be ready to train
Elora 你甚至可以用它来训练
Elora and you can even use that to train
常规的梦想靴 或文本
a regular dream boot or a textual
反转梦境引导以及
inversion dream boot as well
再见
bye